This is me commenting on Muriel Bowser capitulating officially.
She's going to allow for Trump to keep federal troops in D.C.
even after the state of emergency is over.
This person, Chef D.J. Johnson, says this ain't your business.
I want to point a few things out to anybody who is agreeing with the nonsense
that the chef here is cooking up.
First of all, D.C. is the capital of the United States.
It's all of our business.
Second of all, I pay federal taxes.
D.C. is funded in part by federal taxes.
So it literally is my business.
But third, this is happening in D.C. as a beginning.
We already see Mayor Johnson of Chicago rallying the people of Chicago to say,
yo, when he come through, we got to stand up.
We don't want no tanks down here.
And bonus, any injustice anywhere is my business.
Yeah.
But guess what, Chef D.J. Johnson?
In an occupied city, she going to put you out of business.
He's a goofy.
Don't think like him.
You're damn rude, eh?